

SHUBHAM RANI

Software Developer

I am a competent software developer with more than 2 years of solid work experience in development for agency client. I have worked effectively both independently and as part of a team, and I am capable of being highly productive either way.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer SMD Webtech Pvt. Ltd.

Nov. 2023 - Present

Responsibilities

- Responsible for coding on Java, Spring
- Gained hands-on experience in developing Web applications. Assisted senior developer and enhanced problems solving skills. Collaborated with team to optimize existing code.
- Responsible for coding on Bootstrap.
- Responsible for coding on Java Script.
- Responsible for working on HTML Templates.
- Responsible for coding on HTML.
- Responsible for coding on CSS.

Systems Engineer Infosys Ltd.

Mar. 2022 - Oct. 2023

Responsibilities

- Responsible for coding on Java, Spring, Struts, Hibernate
- Responsible for working on HTML Templates.
- Responsible for coding on HTML
- Responsible for coding on CSS.
- Responsible for coding on Bootstrap.

CONTACT

- 6263699865
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/shu bham-rani-89b75a257
- shubhamranii14@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Java
- Spring
- Struts
- Hibernate
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- MySQL
- MS Office

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering
Trinity Institute of Technology & Research
College, Bhopal
2016 – 2020

Intermediate (10+2) S.R.R.S Senior Secondary School, Patna Bihar 2014 – 2016

Matriculation (10) S.R.R.S High School, Bihar 2013

CERTIFICATES

- Infosys Certified MySQL Associate
- Infosys Certified PL/SQL Associate
- Infosys Certified AWA Cloud Practitioner
- Infosys Certified CPQ Developer
- IBM Plum Certification

EXTRA CURRICULUM ACTIVITIES

CSR (Corporate Social Responsibilities)

Activities in Infosys

- Establishes Library set up at---Bhagwati high school and Sweet life ideal education Niketan.
- Volunteer at cyber security event organised by Odisha police.

INTERESTS

Travelling	Net Surfing	Listening Music
Online Game	S Cooking	